Katsiaryna Symanovich OA Engineer

QA Engineer Belarus, Minsk





Katsiaryna_Symanovich



@katsiaryna-symanovich

symanovichkatsiaryna@gmail.com

Summary

Solution-oriented, motivated specialist with extensive technical skills and education. Aimed at highly effective teamwork using excellent communication skills.

Languages

English: Pre-Intermediate – Intermediate

I'm taking the English courses and constantly learning by myself.

Additional Education (certificates)

QA Engineer

Author's courses of QA by Vadim Ksendzov \underline{link} 07/2021 – 10/2021

Tester courses from scratch by Artsiom Rusau on youtube 07/2021

uTest Academy

Education

Systems engineer

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

2017 (Bachelor degree)

Technician-programmer

Minsk Radioengineering College 2007 (Associate degree)

Work Experience

Junior QA Engineer (Practice)

Author's course by Vadim Ksendzov (capital.com) 07/2021-present

During the courses were applied:

Manual testing, Functional testing, API testing (Postman), Load testing (Jmeter), Localization testing of mobile apps.

Crowdtesting

Applause

2020-2021

Writing <u>bug reports</u>, running test cases, collecting logs, capturing video of the device screen, screenshots, the AI Video Collection on the projects: <u>shop.lululemon.com</u>, <u>mylifebox.com</u>, <u>claires.com</u>, Artificial Intelligence system.

Technician-programmer

BA Konkurs

2010-present

Preparation of tenders and processing of results (accepting applications, maintaining a database, eliminating inconsistencies between the declared and actual quantities, preparing data for processing), preparing calculations and reports for holding tenders, maintaining PCs and office equipment

Skills

OKIII3
• Check Lists <u>link1</u> , <u>link2</u>
• Bug Reports <u>link</u>
• SQL <u>link</u>
• Postman <u>link</u>
- sending requests (GET, POST, PUT, DELETE), creating an environment, launching a collection;
 writing autotests: checking the answer, checking the json structure, transferring numbers to the environment, checking the coefficients, comparing numbers, checking the correctness of the received values
• Git, GitHublink
Working with local and remote repositories (creating / deleting a repository, files, branches; adding files to Git, creating commits, merging to the main branch, connecting an SSH key).
• LINUX commandslink
cd, ls, pwd, mkdir, touch, find, rm, cat, rmdir, mv, tail, grep, less, date, sudo, curl, chmod, head
• Charles <u>link</u> , Fiddler <u>link</u>
Installing a certificate, configuring a proxy server, intercepting and analyzing traffic.
• JavaScript (basics)
For writing tests in Postman to check the response from the server.
Android Studio
Run apps on the Android Emulator and a real device.
• ADB
Connecting the device via wi-fi, install / uninstall application, capturing log files, taking screenshots.
• DevTools (Google Chrome)

• Jmeter.....<u>link</u>

Basic knowledges of Load testing, Spike.

• HTML, CSS